https://www.fundforanimals.org/about/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
The Fund for Animals is committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information private. You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any identifying information about yourself. However, because our website includes areas in which visitors can provide personally identifying information, we have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and practices regarding information we collect about you.
This Privacy Policy governs certain electronic communications maintained and distributed by the Fund for Animals for the benefit of its members and other visitors interested in the protection of all animals. Our headquarters is located at 1255 23rd Street NW, Suite 460, Washington, DC 20037. The Fund for Animals reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be preceded by a notice posted to this Privacy Policy at least 10 days prior to the effective date of such change.
How We Collect Information About You
Information You Voluntarily Provide: The Fund for Animals and its affiliates, including the Humane Society of the United States (HSUS), collect and maintain certain personal information about you when you send us an email or complete any of our online forms, such as when you request information from us, make a donation, request to become a member or forward a webpage, electronic postcard or electronic ballot. Such information may include your name, mailing address, email address and other information collected in the forms. You may be asked to provide credit card information to become a member, contribute, purchase certain information or materials or subscribe to various publications.
Other Information: We also collect certain other information that cannot identify you personally when you visit our websites. This information includes your IP address and your domain name. We log these IP addresses and domain names and aggregate them for system administration and to monitor the use of our sites. We use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our sites, the average time spent on our sites, the number of pages viewed and various other site statistics. This monitoring helps us to provide a more useful and engaging online experience to site visitors and helps us to improve the quality of our content.
The Fund for Animals and its affiliates use cookies to make the results available for your on-site searches. Cookies are not used for any other reason on our sites. A cookie is a small file that is sent out by a website, accepted by the user's browser and placed on the user's hard drive. You can always set your browser to warn of cookies being placed and then choose which cookies you want to accept. We do not match any information gathered by cookies with personal information you may have voluntarily submitted to any of our websites.
The HSUS uses remarketing with Google AdWords and analytics to display content specific advertisements to visitors that have previously visited our site when those visitors go to other websites that have the Google Display Network implemented. The HSUS also uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.
Ways Information About You Is Used
We may use the information you voluntarily provided to contact you regarding animal-related issues we feel you may be interested in, to keep you updated regarding our programs and to extend an invitation to you to support our programs. From time to time, we may make such voluntary information, excluding credit card information (which will never be disclosed), available to the Fund for Animals' affiliates, including the HSUS, or to sponsors or licensees that provide special programs or services we think you might find interesting or beneficial. We use very strict standards in determining which reputable companies become sponsors and licensees to ensure that such organizations are committed to the protection of visitors' privacy and committed to our animal protection goals. In addition, we may use, disclose or transfer your personal information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, acquisition, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our operations or assets (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
If your personal information will be used in any manner other than as stated above, such use shall be specifically posted. If you wish to update or remove your information, or if you do not wish your information to be shared with affiliated third parties, please email us. You may also unsubscribe at any time by following a link included in every email we send you.
Other
From time to time, the Fund for Animals may link to other websites not affiliated with the Fund for Animals. We attempt to link only to those websites which also respect a visitor's privacy and our animal protection goals. However, we cannot be responsible for the content or policies of third-party websites. Please check with these third-party organizations or companies for their specific privacy policies. If you find inoperable links or are concerned about any of the sites that we currently link to, please inform us.
Security
The Fund for Animals uses generally accepted, industry-standard security systems, software and encryption technologies, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), for the secure transfer of personal and financial data and to protect against unauthorized access to the Fund for Animals servers, equipment and other components of our online presence. This includes using industry-standard security systems to protect credit card processing information. Our web servers are stored off-site at multiple, physically secure facilities with limited access.
Contacting the Fund for Animals
If you would like to contact us about correcting information we might have collected or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us or write to us at:
The Fund for Animals
Attn: Webmaster
1255 23rd Street NW, Suite 460
Washington, DC 20037
Share
